sportingbet.com.au 2010-05-14

# Sportingbet Australia

The following statement sets out Sportingbet Australia's policy relating to the collection, storage and use of personal information in the course of its business.

Our purpose is to assure anyone who does business with us that Sportingbet Australia will comply with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) ("Privacy Act"). 

This Privacy Policy is in addition to Sportingbet Australia's Betting Terms and Conditions and should be read in conjunction with such Betting Terms and Conditions. 

Sportingbet Australia reviews its Privacy Policy from time to time and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify this policy at any time without notice. 

You should review this page periodically so that you are updated on any changes to the policy.   
  
SPORTINGBET AUSTRALIA IS COMPLIANT WITH THE NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLES  
  
Sportingbet Australia takes seriously its obligation to safeguard personal information about its customers.

Sportingbet Australia is committed to complying with the National Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act.   
  
WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
  
We collect a variety of personal information in the course of our business.

We only collect personal information to the extent that it is necessary to our business practices.

Sportingbet Australia will collect information only by lawful and fair means. 

Sportingbet Australia is required to collect personal information under law, for example, laws relating to financial transactions, taxation and sportsbetting control. 

We may also record other information including responses to competitions, give-aways and other promotions.  
  
HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION  
  
Sportingbet Australia collects personal information from our customers for the purpose of providing services to those customers. 

We may also use contact details for the purpose of sending information about products and services to our customers.

Unless you consent, use of your personal information will be related to the primary reason for collection and, only if you would reasonably expect it to occur, would your personal information be used for a secondary purpose or if it is required or authorised by law or otherwise permitted under the Privacy Act.  
  
TO WHOM PERSONAL INFORMATION IS DISCLOSED  
  
Sportingbet Australia does not sell personal information to other companies.

There are limited circumstances in which external organisations may be given access to your personal information. One circumstance is where an Australian governing sporting body requests information of a Client who joined Sportingbet Australia after September 1, 2006 and that information will only be provided to assist in a legitimate inquiry conducted by the Australian governing sporting body to maintain the integrity of the sport. Other circumstances where a Client consents for Sportingbet to disclose personal information and as permitted by the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) are set out below. The information may be used or disclosed:

  1. to enable Sportingbet to perform its obligations to the Client under Sportingbet's Rules;
  2. to enable Sportingbet to ensure that the Client performs their obligations under Sportingbet's Rules;
  3. to a credit reporting agency;
  4. to maintain a credit information file in relation to the Client;
  5. to carry out a credit assessment on the Client;
  6. for planning, research, promotion and marketing of our products and services;
  7. to organisations associated with the provision of our services, such as associated data centres, for marketing and analysis purposes;
  8. to a potential purchaser of, or investor in any business conducted by Sportingbet;
  9. to law enforcement agencies to assist in the prevention of criminal activities.

We require these organisations to agree to our Privacy Policy and to strict conditions governing how this information may be used. We will give you a way to ["opt-in/opt-out"] of being contacted for promotional purposes by us and any third parties.  
  
SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
  
Sportingbet Australia will take reasonable steps to protect personal information we collect and ensure that it is accurate, complete and up-to-date. 

Your information is held on secure servers.

Our employees, agents, contractors are required to maintain the confidentiality of all personal information.   
  
ACCESS TO AND CORRECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION  
  
If you think that any personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date, please contact our Privacy Officer (see below for contact details) and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that it is corrected.

We may require personal identification.   
  
AUSTRALIAN FEDERAL PRIVACY COMMISSIONER'S WEBSITE  
  
For further information about privacy issues in Australia, visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's website.

If you have any queries please contact Sportingbet.
